

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Well-qualified Strategic Senior Human
Resources Manager with proven
success in improving operations and solving
problems. Energetic, self-motivated, diligent &
mature HR professional with rich experience of
15+ years in different Industry and organizations.
Developed excellent skill of Understanding
Organization requirement, and accordingly
developing and implementing necessary strategy
within the organization,
Certified in Design Thinking.

CORE SKILLS

- Learning & developments
- People Management
- Employee Engagement
- HR Transformation
- Rewards & Recognition
- Succession Planning
- Change Management
- Employee Grievances
- Competency planning
- Performance Management

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Aspiring for challenging
 assignments in Human Resource
 Management with an organization
 of repute ~ Skilled in identifying &
 hiring through various sources,
 handling end-to-end recruitment
 cycle and maintaining cordial
 relationship with the employees

Varsha Ravi Kulkarni

8087098000

✓ varshakulkarni1980.vk@gmail.com

Pune,411014

EXPERIENCE

12/2015 - Current

Blue Dart Express Ltd | Pune

Branch Manager-Human Resource Pune & Rest Maharashtra(Nagpur, Raipur, Chhattisgarh, Goa, Aurangabad & Kolhapur)

- Talent Acquisition for Pune & Rest Maharashtra and 2 state Chhattisgarh, Goa
- Core HR Operations- Analytical Data driven approach & Reporting.
- Strategic HR Management ,Business Analytics & HR Analytics
- Training & Development as per Organization strategic planning
- Change Management, Succession / Career Planning, Organization Development
- Employee Relation & Grievances
- KRA & KPI based PMS system Execution
- Employee Rewards and retention and OD initiatives for Job Satisfaction
- Conducting company -wide Open House Meeting to Convey Updates
- Handling full Employee Life cycle from Recruitment to Full & Final Settlement

04/2013 - 12/2015

Tata Trent Hypermarket Ltd |Pune

HR Manager

12/2011 - 04/2013

Parc Estique, A 5 Star Hotel | Pune

Assistant Human Resource Manager

06/2009 - 12/2011

The O Hotel | Pune

Sr. HR Executive.

12/2007 - 05/2009

Oxford Properties| Pune,

Executive Secretary

EDUCATION

2013

Neville Wadia College, Pune University | Pune

Masters in Personnel Management (MBA -HR)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Personal Details: DOB: 14th July ,1980

Residential Address: Flat No.64,Dhalia Building, Neco Garden, Viman Nagar Pune-411014(Maharashtra) 2004

Narlakar Institute, Pune University | Pune

Masters in Computer Management: Computer Management

2002

St.Mira Collage for Girls | Pune

B.Com

LANGUAGES

English, Marathi, Hindi: First Language

Afrikaans: C2

Proficient